Jonah Sherman Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 1. Business file, 1700 - 1984; 1; Boxes: 1 - 30
  - Subseries 1.7: Utilities, 1911 - 1962; 1.7; Boxes: 24 - 25
    - Central Hudson Gas and Electric, undated (Folder 3, Box 25)
    - Central Hudson Gas and Electric, undated (Folder 4, Box 25)
  - Subseries 1.8: Miscellany, 1700 - 1984; 1.8; Boxes: 25 - 30
    Series containes materials for Businesses and reciepts and checks
    By Subject
    - Subseries 1.8.1: Businesses, 1870 - 1984; 1.8.1; Boxes: 25 - 29
      - A.B. Stockholm, undated (Folder 5, Box 25)
      - Adriance Moline, circa 1920s (Folder 6, Box 25)
      - Adriance, Platt Co, 1869-1900 (Folder 7, Box 25)
      - Adraince Platt Catalogs, 1884 (Folder 8, Box 25)
      - Adriance Platt, 1875 - 1888 (Folder 9, Box 25)
      - Alertric, undated (Folder 10, Box 25)
      - Allen Bros, undated (Folder 11, Box 25)
      - John A. Alley, 1974 (Folder 12, Box 25)
      - Ambler, undated (Folder 13, Box 25)
      - American Express, 1899 (Folder 14, Box 25)
      - Andes, undated (Folder 15, Box 25)
      - Luther Andres, 1799 (Folder 16, Box 25)
      - Arnold Mitchell, 1874 (Folder 17, Box 25)
      - Atlantic Pacific, undated (Folder 18, Box 25)
      - Arax Photographers, undated (Folder 19, Box 25)
      - Army e Navy, 1942 (Folder 20, Box 25)
      - Audio Fixit Centre, 1974 (Folder 21, Box 25)
      - J.D. Barnum, 1881 (Folder 22, Box 25)
      - Barnett Rubin, 1926 - 1951 (Folder 23, Box 25)
      - Bartlett Steam Cracker, 1871 - 1873 (Folder 24, Box 25)
      - William C. Bauer, 1899 (Folder 25, Box 25)
      - Beacon Cleaners, undated (Folder 1, Box 26)
      - Ben-Pari Co, undated (Folder 2, Box 26)
      - J. Blankenhorn son, 1875 (Folder 3, Box 26)
      - Stain Bloomer, undated (Folder 4, Box 26)
      - Bolton Surgical, undated (Folder 5, Box 26)
      - Bonner Motors, undated (Folder 6, Box 26)
      - Bushnell's, undated (Folder 7, Box 26)
      - R.V. Cables, undated (Folder 8, Box 26)
      - John N. Candee, undated (Folder 9, Box 26)
      - Cash Grocery, undated (Folder 10, Box 26)
      - Chapinville Wheel Co, undated (Folder 11, Box 26)
      - Clark's O.N.T. Spool Cotton, undated (Folder 12, Box 26)
      - Coe Deyo, undated (Folder 13, Box 26)
      - Collingwood Seaman, 1944 (Folder 14, Box 26)
      - The Colonial, 1916 (Folder 15, Box 26)
      - T. Connelly, 1875 (Folder 16, Box 26)
      - Consolidated Dry Goods Co, undated (Folder 17, Box 26)
      - C.W. Coons, 1897 (Folder 18, Box 26)
      - Crowley's Dairy Products, undated (Folder 19, Box 26)
      - Crown Cleaner Dryer, undated (Folder 20, Box 26)
      - Cundy Caire, undated (Folder 21, Box 26)
      - Cundy, E.W., undated (Folder 22, Box 26)
      - Dail Sutton, 1949 (Folder 23, Box 26)
      - DeLaval, 1910 - 1942 (Folder 24, Box 26)
      - DeLaval, undated (Folder 25, Box 26)
      - Charles De Paris, undated (Folder 26, Box 26)
      - De's Jewelers, undated (Folder 27, Box 26)
      - DeSoto Service, undated (Folder 28, Box 26)
      - Diesing Supply Co, undated (Folder 29, Box 26)
      - P.C. Doherty, undated (Folder 30, Box 26)
      - Donald, Converse Maynard, undated (Folder 31, Box 26)
      - Dr. D. Jayne's, 1922 (Folder 32, Box 26)
      - Dutchess Manufacturing Co, 1887 - 1916 (Folder 33, Box 26)
      - Dutton Lumber, 1961 (Folder 34, Box 26)
      - Eighmie, 1882 (Folder 35, Box 26)
      - Louis Elting Sons, undated (Folder 36, Box 26)
      - Charles Erhard, 1904 (Folder 37, Box 26)
      - Fallkill Manufacturing Co, 1887 (Folder 38, Box 26)
      - Otto Faust, 1899 (Folder 39, Box 26)
      - Fargo, undated (Folder 40, Box 26)
      - The Federal Bearings Co. Inc, undated (Folder 41, Box 26)
      - FIAT, undated (Folder 1, Box 27)
      - Fitchett Bros, undated (Folder 2, Box 27)
      - Fleishman's Fine Furniture, undated (Folder 3, Box 27)
      - Freer's Laundry and Dry Cleaning, undated (Folder 4, Box 27)
      - Arthur L. Fried, undated (Folder 5, Box 27)
      - Wm. Frost Son, undated (Folder 6, Box 27)
      - C. H. Gallup, photographer, undated (Folder 7, Box 27)
      - The Garden Tailoring Shop, undated (Folder 9, Box 27)
      - Gellert, undated (Folder 9, Box 27)
      - Gifford Sherman Innis, 1885 (Folder 10, Box 27)
      - Gildersleeve Co, undated (Folder 11, Box 27)
      - Gloede, undated (Folder 12, Box 27)
      - F.J. Goes Grocer, 1911 (Folder 13, Box 27)
      - Gotlieb, 1952 (Folder 14, Box 27)
      - F. H. Grobe Son, 1891 (Folder 15, Box 27)
      - Hadderfield, 1898 (Folder 16, Box 27)
      - Haight Dudley, 1889 (Folder 17, Box 27)
      - Hamilton Reproduction Inc, undated (Folder 18, Box 27)
      - Hanford Eggleston Co, 1900 (Folder 19, Box 27)
      - Hansman, Pralow Winter, undated (Folder 20, Box 27)
      - Chas D. Henderson, undated (Folder 21, Box 27)
      - Hoe Wrench, undated (Folder 22, Box 27)
      - Hoffman Co, 1885 (Folder 23, Box 27)
      - Hong Kong Shanghai Banking Corporation, 1898 (Folder 24, Box 27)
      - The House of Appliances, undated (Folder 25, Box 27)
      - The Hudson Lunch, 1905 (Folder 26, Box 27)
      - Humphrey Druggist, undated (Folder 27, Box 27)
      - IBM, 1954 - 1959 (Folder 28, Box 27)
      - Frank Incremona, undated (Folder 29, Box 27)
      - George Innis, circa 1860s (Folder 30, Box 27)
      - Joscap Realty Corporation (Joscap/Josecap/Jacton), circa 1958 (Folder 31, Box 27)
      - Koth Bayer, undated (Folder 32, Box 27)
      - Lane Brothers, 1914 (Folder 33, Box 27)
      - Lane Farm Supply, undated (Folder 34, Box 27)
      - Langsing- Broas Printing Co., undated (Folder 35, Box 27)
      - Lansing Company, undated (Folder 36, Box 27)
      - William J. Leahey, 1910 (Folder 37, Box 27)
      - Lewis Store, undated (Folder 38, Box 27)
      - Lindmark's bookstore, 1942 - 1943 (Folder 39, Box 27)
      - Little Businessmen, undated (Folder 40, Box 27)
      - Loedy Loedy, undated (Folder 41, Box 27)
      - MacDonald Beatty, undated (Folder 42, Box 27)
      - Charles F. McGregor, undated (Folder 43, Box 27)
      - Midtown Pharmacy, 1957 (Folder 44, Box 27)
      - Millard and Son, undated (Folder 45, Box 27)
      - Peter Miller Sons Shoes, undated (Folder 46, Box 27)
      - Harold S. Mills, undated (Folder 47, Box 27)
      - Molloy Pharmacy, 1971 (Folder 48, Box 27)
      - Moore Brothers, undated (Folder 49, Box 27)
      - Morgan Lake Ice Co., 1872 (Folder 50, Box 27)
      - Oake's Spring, 1909 (Folder 1, Box 28)
      - A.P. Ordway Co, undated (Folder 2, Box 28)
      - Patterson Auto Sales, undated (Folder 3, Box 28)
      - Peary, undated (Folder 4, Box 28)
      - Pierce's, 1876 - 1894 (Folder 5, Box 28)
      - Phoenix Horse Shoe Co, 1926 (Folder 6, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie - Downtown Businesses, 1991 (Folder 7, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie Chair Co., 1901 (Folder 8, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie Cracker Bakery, 1897 - 1898 (Folder 9, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie Foundry Machine Co, 1872 - 1889 (Folder 10, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie Laundry and Dry Cleaning, undated (Folder 11, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie Pottery Drain Pipes Works, 1870 (Folder 12, Box 28)
      - Poughkeepsie Underwear Co, undated (Folder 13, Box 28)
      - S.W. Raymond, undated (Folder 14, Box 28)
      - The Real Estate Journal, 1891 (Folder 15, Box 28)
      - Reed Forman, undated (Folder 16, Box 28)
      - W.T. Reynolds, 1919 (Folder 17, Box 28)
      - H.W. Richardson, undated (Folder 18, Box 28)
      - The Saltford Flower Shop, undated (Folder 19, Box 28)
      - E. J. Sanders, undated (Folder 20, Box 28)
      - Schatz Manufacturing Co, 1921 - 1967 (Folder 21, Box 28)
      - Schatz Manufacturing Company - The Federal Bearings Company, Inc., 1941 (Folder 22, Box 28)
      - J. Schrauth's Sons, undated (Folder 23, Box 28)
      - John Schwartz Sons, 1860 - 1912 (Folder 24, Box 28)
      - Sedwick Machine Works, undated (Folder 25, Box 28)
      - Shaker, Travis Quinn, undated (Folder 1, Box 29)
      - Sherman's Furniture, 1982 (Folder 2, Box 29)
      - M. Shwartz Co, 1982 (Folder 3, Box 29)
      - Silber Dairy, undated (Folder 4, Box 29)
      - R. Slee Co, 1865 (Folder 5, Box 29)
      - Frederick A. Smith, undated (Folder 6, Box 29)
      - Smith Bros., 1918 (Folder 7, Box 29)
      - Smith Brothers, 1947 (Folder 8, Box 29)
      - Staatsburg Tool Company, 1961 - 1984 (Folder 9, Box 29)
      - Standard Gage Company, 1985 (Folder 10, Box 29)
      - Steenson Baker, undated (Folder 11, Box 29)
      - Steenson Van Vlack, undated (Folder 12, Box 29)
      - Sterling Brothers, undated (Folder 13, Box 29)
      - Strain and Sutton., undated (Folder 14, Box 29)
      - Strand Music Shop, undated (Folder 15, Box 29)
      - Taylor Clamps, 1930 - 1953 (Folder 16, Box 29)
      - Trivers Clothes, undated (Folder 17, Box 29)
      - John Van Benschoten, undated (Folder 18, Box 29)
      - Vassar Area Directory, undated (Folder 19, Box 29)
      - Vassar Pharmacy, undated (Folder 20, Box 29)
      - Ceo D. Voge, undated (Folder 21, Box 29)
      - Wallace Co., 1918 - 1959 (Folder 22, Box 29)
      - Warshaw Shoes, undated (Folder 23, Box 29)
      - Wells Coutan, 1898 (Folder 24, Box 29)
      - Whitman Publishing, 1940 (Folder 1, Box 30)
      - Wilber Eureka Mower, 1873 (Folder 2, Box 30)
      - Wolpe Mattress Manufacturing, undated (Folder 3, Box 30)
      - I.C. Wood Brother, 1879 (Folder 4, Box 30)
      - Wood Tittamer, undated (Folder 5, Box 30)
    - Subseries 1.8.2: Receipts and Checks, 1700 - 1949; 1.8.2; Box: 30
      - Receipts and Checks, 1700s (Folder 6, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1811 (Folder 7, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1813 (Folder 8, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1814 (Folder 9, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1830 (Folder 10, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1861 (Folder 11, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1863 (Folder 12, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1868 (Folder 13, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1869 (Folder 14, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1870 (Folder 15, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1871 (Folder 16, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1872 (Folder 17, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1874 (Folder 18, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1875 (Folder 19, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1876 (Folder 20, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1877 (Folder 21, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1878 (Folder 22, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1879 (Folder 23, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1880 (Folder 24, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1881 (Folder 25, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1882 (Folder 26, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1884 (Folder 27, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1885 (Folder 28, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1886 (Folder 29, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1891 (Folder 30, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1892 (Folder 31, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1893 (Folder 32, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1895 (Folder 33, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1899 (Folder 34, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1900 (Folder 35, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1904 (Folder 36, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1906 (Folder 37, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1908 (Folder 38, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1909 (Folder 39, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1910 (Folder 40, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1911 (Folder 41, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1912 (Folder 42, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1914 (Folder 43, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1915 (Folder 44, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1916 (Folder 45, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1917 (Folder 46, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1918 (Folder 47, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1919 (Folder 48, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1920 (Folder 49, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1925 (Folder 50, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1926 (Folder 51, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1927 (Folder 52, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1928 (Folder 53, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1931 (Folder 54, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1932 (Folder 55, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1934 (Folder 56, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1935 (Folder 57, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1937 (Folder 58, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1938 (Folder 59, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1939 (Folder 60, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1941 (Folder 61, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1942 (Folder 62, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1943 (Folder 63, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1947 (Folder 64, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1948 (Folder 65, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1949 (Folder 66, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, 1951 (Folder 67, Box 30)
      - Receipts and Checks, undated (Folder 68, Box 30)
- 2. Topical file, 1799 - 1999; 2; Boxes: 31 - 51
  Series contains Almanacs, Celebrations, Civic Organizations, Government, Histories, Law offices, Recreation, Religion, Transportation, Urban planning, and Miscellany
  - Subseries 2.1: Almanacs, 1868 - 1930; 2.1; Box: 31
    By Type
    - Farmers' Almanac for Dutchess and Ulster Counties (3 copies), 1868 (Folder 1, Box 31)
    - Farmers' Almanac for Dutchess and Ulster Counties, 1869 (Folder 2, Box 31)
    - Farmers' Almanac, 1908 (Folder 3, Box 31)
    - Farmers' Almanac for Dutchess and Ulster Counties, 1930 (Folder 4, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Almanac for 1885 (Folder 5, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Almanac for 1887 (Folder 6, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1891 (2 copies) (Folder 7, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1892 (Folder 8, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1893 (Folder 9, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1894 (Folder 10, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1895 (2 copies) (Folder 11, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1896 (Folder 12, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1897 (Folder 13, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1898 (Folder 14, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1899 (Folder 15, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1900 (Folder 16, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1901 (Folder 17, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1903 (Folder 18, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1904 (Folder 19, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1905 (Folder 20, Box 31)
    - Poughkeepsie Eagle Diary-Almanac for 1924 (Folder 21, Box 31)
    - Weekly Enterprise Annual for 1891 (Folder 22, Box 31)
  - Subseries 2.2: Celebrations, 1876 - 1987; 2.2; Boxes: 32 - 36
    Series contains materials for 300th Anniversary Parade and Other celebrations
    - Subseries 2.2.1: 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987; 2.2.1; Boxes: 32 - 35
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 1, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 2, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 3, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 4, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 5, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 6, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 7, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 8, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 9, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 10, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 11, Box 32)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 1, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 2, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 3, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 4, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 5, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 6, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 7, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 8, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 9, Box 33)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 1, Box 34)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 2, Box 34)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 3, Box 34)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 4, Box 34)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade, 1987 June (Folder 5, Box 34)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade - Hudson Valley Magazine, 1987 June (Folder 6, Box 34)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade Booklet, 1987 (Folder 7, Box 34)
      - Photographs of Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade (items moved to Graphic Materials), 1987 June (Folder 8, Box 34)
      - Ribbon 1 - Parade General Chairman sash, 1987 June (Folder 1, Box 35)
      - Ribbon 2 - Red Committee badge, 1987 June (Folder 2, Box 35)
      - Ribbon 3 - White Dignitary badge, 1987 June (Folder 3, Box 35)
      - Ribbon 4 - Blue Official badge, 1987 June (Folder 4, Box 35)
      - Ribbon 5 - Yellow Riverfest badge, 1987 June (Folder 5, Box 35)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade Hat - '300 Years of People, Pride Progress, 1987 June (Folder 6, Box 35)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade T-Shirt - '300 Years of People, Pride Progress, 1987 June (Folder 7, Box 35)
      - Poughkeepsie's 300th Anniversary Parade Pepsi Can - '300 Years of People, Pride Progress, 1987 June (Folder 8, Box 35)
      - Spoon labeled, 'Dutchess Room - Poughkeepsie Inn', 1987 June (Folder 9, Box 35)
    - Subseries 2.2.2: Other celebrations, 1876 - 1987; 2.2.2; Box: 36
      - U.S. Centenary, 1876 (Folder 1, Box 36)
      - Hudson-Fulton Anniversaries, 1909 (Folder 2, Box 36)
      - Fourth of July, 1919 (Folder 3, Box 36)
      - Rhinebeck Centenary, 1934 (Folder 4, Box 36)
      - 250th Anniversary of the Van Kleeck Homestead, 1937 (Folder 5, Box 36)
      - 150th Anniversary of the U.S. Constitution, 1938 (Folder 6, Box 36)
      - 350th Anniversary of Henry Hudson, 1959 (Folder 7, Box 36)
      - 300th Anniversary of Poughkeepsie, 1987 (Folder 8, Box 36)
  - Subseries 2.3: Civic Organizations, 1883 - 1990; 2.3; Boxes: 36 - 37
    - Amrita Club, 1883 - 1932 (Folder 9, Box 36)
    - Fire companies, 1888 - 1918 (Folder 10, Box 36)
    - Hospitals and Health, 1880 - 1947 (Folder 11, Box 36)
    - Poughkeepsie Chamber of Commerce, 1912 - 1969 (Folder 12, Box 36)
    - Poughkeepsie Chamber of Commerce, 1918 - 1997 (Folder 13, Box 36)
    - Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, circa 1850 - 1990 (Folder 14, Box 36)
    - Civic organizations - Miscellany, 1870 - 1989 (Folder 15, Box 36)
    - Civic organizations - Miscellany, 1892 - 1968 (Folder 1, Box 37)
  - Subseries 2.4: Education, 1863 - 1983; 2.4; Boxes: 37 - 44
    Series contains materials for Eastman Business College, Vassar College, Other Educational Institutions, and Schoolbooks
    - Subseries 2.4.1: Eastman Business College, 1863 - 1924; 2.4.1; Boxes: 37 - 39
      Alphabetical and Chronological
      - Admissions, circa 1878 - 1905 (Folder 2, Box 37)
      - Autograph book, 1883 (Folder 3, Box 37)
      - Catalogue and Prospectus, circa 1905 (Folder 4, Box 37)
      - College Catalogue, undated (Folder 5, Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1867 (Folder 6, Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1877 - 1878 (Folder 7, Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1894 - 1899 (Folder 8, Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1905 (Folder 9, Box 37)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Folder 10, Box 37)
      - Correspondence, undated (Folder 11, Box 37)
      - Coursework of R.L. Cone, 1871 (Folder 12, Box 37)
      - Coursework of R.L. Cone, 1878 (Folder 13, Box 37)
      - Coursework of R.L. Cone, 1879 (Folder 14, Box 37)
      - Coursework of R.L. Cone, undated (Folder 15, Box 37)
      - Coursework of R.S. Cone, 1872 (Folder 1, Box 38)
      - Coursework of R.S. Cone, 1878 - 1879 (Folder 2, Box 38)
      - Coursework of R.S. Cone, 1878 - 1879 (Folder 3, Box 38)
      - Coursework of R.S. Cone, 1879 (Folder 4, Box 38)
      - Coursework of R.S. Cone, 1879 (Folder 5, Box 38)
      - Coursework of R.S. Cone, 1879 (Folder 6, Box 38)
      - The Eastman-Gaines Schools and their Environment, circa 1915 (Folder 7, Box 38)
      - Events, 1877 - 1879 (Folder 8, Box 38)
      - Events, 1883 - 1884 (Folder 9, Box 38)
      - Events, 1893 - 1898 (Folder 10, Box 38)
      - In memory of Hon. H.G. Eastman, LL.D., 1878 (Folder 11, Box 38)
      - Lectures, 1897 (Folder 12, Box 38)
      - Lectures, 1916 (Folder 13, Box 38)
      - Lectures, undated (Folder 14, Box 38)
      - Merchant's Guide, 1884 (Folder 15, Box 38)
      - Notebook with records of deceased patients' afflictions, 1863 (Folder 16, Box 38)
      - Property Auction, 1873 (Folder 17, Box 38)
      - Records and Finance, 1863 - 1864 (Folder 18, Box 38)
      - Records and Finance, 1878 - 1879 (Folder 19, Box 38)
      - Records and Finance, circa 1870s (Folder 20, Box 38)
      - Records and Finance, 1883 (Folder 21, Box 38)
      - Records and Finance, 1890 - 1898 (Folder 1, Box 39)
      - Records and Finance, 1900 (Folder 2, Box 39)
      - Records and Finance, undated (Folder 3, Box 39)
      - Self-Defense of Expelled Students, 1865 (Folder 4, Box 39)
      - Students and curriculum, 1908 - 1924 (Folder 5, Box 39)
      - Student's Guide, 1878 (Folder 6, Box 39)
      - Student Handbook, 1889 (Folder 7, Box 39)
      - Miscellany, undated (Folder 8, Box 39)
      - Other formats, various (Folder 9, Box 39)
    - Subseries 2.4.2: Vassar College, 1867 - 1983; 2.4.2; Boxes: 39 - 42
      - Alumni, 1952 (Folder 10, Box 39)
      - Alumni, 1958 - 1971 (Folder 11, Box 39)
      - Alumni, 1977 (Folder 12, Box 39)
      - Archives and Special Collections, undated (Folder 13, Box 39)
      - Catalogue, 1867 - 1868 (Folder 14, Box 39)
      - Catalogue, 1873 (Folder 15, Box 39)
      - Catalogue, 1879 - 1880 (Folder 16, Box 39)
      - Catalogue, 1885 - 1886 (Folder 1, Box 40)
      - Catalogue, 1898 - 1899 (Folder 2, Box 40)
      - Catalogue, 1904 - 1905 (Folder 3, Box 40)
      - Catalogue, 1982 - 1983 (Folder 4, Box 40)
      - Catalogue, 1990 - 1991 (Folder 5, Box 40)
      - Catalogue, 1991 - 1992 (Folder 6, Box 40)
      - Events, 1869 (Folder 7, Box 40)
      - Events, 1875 (Folder 8, Box 40)
      - Events, 1893 - 1898 (Folder 9, Box 40)
      - Events, 1911 (Folder 10, Box 40)
      - Events, 1977 (Folder 11, Box 40)
      - Events, 1977 - 1978 (Folder 1, Box 41)
      - Events, 1981 - 1986 (Folder 2, Box 41)
      - Events, 1990 - 1992 (Folder 3, Box 41)
      - Events, 1990 - 1992 (Folder 4, Box 41)
      - Pamphlets, 1872 - 1888 (Folder 5, Box 41)
      - Pamphlets, 1921 - 1931 (Folder 6, Box 41)
      - Pamphlets, 1975 (Folder 7, Box 41)
      - Student Handbook, 1905 (Folder 8, Box 41)
      - Student Handbook, 1951 (Folder 9, Box 41)
      - Trusteeship and Finance, 1969 - 1986 (Folder 10, Box 41)
      - "Vassar," drawn by Anne Cleveland and Jean Anderson, 1938 (Folder 11, Box 41)
      - Vassarion, 1892 (Folder 12, Box 41)
      - Vassarion, 1900 (Folder 13, Box 41)
      - Vassarion, 1904 (Folder 1, Box 42)
      - Vassarion, 1905 (Folder 2, Box 42)
      - Vassarion, 1922 (Folder 3, Box 42)
      - Miscellany, 1897 - circa 2007 (Folder 4, Box 42)
    - Subseries 2.4.3: Other Educational Institutions, 1851 - 1976; 2.4.3; Boxes: 42 - 43
      Alphabetical by School